Women's Liberation Collection, 1959-2006
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- BOOKS
  - Womancraft: The Conscious Development of Psychic Skills We All Possess by Diane Mariechild, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Self-Defense: Instructor and Participant Guide by Linda Sattem, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Feminist Wicca: Catalog, 1979 (Box 25)
  - How To Go To Work When Your Husband Is Against It…by Felice N. Schwartz, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Amazon Odyssey by Ti-Grace Atkinson, 1974 (Box 25)
  - The Greasy Thumb Automechanics Manual For Women by Barb Wyatt, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Loose on Shelf
    - 50-50 Gender Balance: Why We Have to "get-it" and get it now!, Angela Z. Allen, 2009 (Box 25)
    - Women at Work: An Annotated Bibliography by Mei Liang Bickner, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Unbecoming Men, Mike Bradley, et al., 1971 (Box 25)
    - I'm Running Away From Home But I'm not Allowed to Cross the Street, Gabrielle Burton, 1972 (Box 25)
    - The PMS Conspiracy, Felicity Artemis Flowes, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Everything Men Know About Women, Dr. Alan Francis, undated (Box 25)
    - Gender Advertisements by Irving Goffman, 1979 (Box 25)
    - The New Woman's Survival Catalog: A Woman-made Book by Susan Rennie and Kirsten Grimstad, 1973 (Box 25)
    - Sisterhood is Powerful, edited by Robin Morgan, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Sisterhood is Forever, edited by Ruth Morgan, 2003 (Box 25)
    - The Philosophy of Misogyny: Power, Myth and Silence in the U.S. During the 1950's by Linda Nelson 1983 (Box 25)
    - Guidelines to Feminist Consciousness Raising, Harriet Pearl and Gay Abarbanell, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Feminist Revolution, Redstockings, 1975 (Box 25)
    - Women's Liberation and Revolution, Sheila Rowbothem, 1972 (Box 25)
    - Women: A Book for Men produced by James Wagenvoord and Peyton Bailey, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Woman Power: The Movement for Women's Liberation by Cellestine Ware, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Channeling Children, Women on Words and Images, 1975 (Box 25)